Guide to the Brooklyn periodical illustrations BCMS.0003
Brooklyn Collection
- Industry
  - Henry Lawrence & Sons, Manufacturer of Cordage and Bagging; Office, 192 Front Street, Near Fulton, New York. Factory, Bushwick Avenue, Brooklyn, E.D. Verso: Lawrence Waterbury & Co., Cordage Manufacturers, Brooklyn, E.D., New York, Office and Warerooms, 136 Front St., New York, 1876 (Box 8)
  - Higgins' German Laundry. The American Grocer, 1881-02-24 (Box 8)
  - Holmes' Barrel Making Machinery. –The Chamfering and Crozing Machine [various ill.]. Scientific American, 1874-03-28 (Box 8)
  - J.S. Loomis' Moulding and Planing Mills. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - James Weir's Conservatories and Green-Houses. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - John Good's Ropemaking Machinery Establishment. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - Lawrence Waterbury & Co. Cordage & Cotton Bagging Manufacturing. Atlantic Publishing & Engraving Co., New York, undated. (Box 8)
  - The Lidgerwood Manufacturing Company, New York. Hoisting Engines and Boilers—Gorton Heaters. Scientific American, 1888-06-02 (Box 8)
  - The Manufacture of Electrical Machines by the Fuller Electrical Company, at their Factory in Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1882-04-01 (Box 8)
  - Martin Worn & Son's Furniture Warehouse. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - New Beam Engine Built at Continental Works, Greenpoint, Brooklyn, N.Y. Scientific American, 1881-12-31 (Box 8)
  - New Method of Docking and Excavating Canals. Scientific American, 1872-10-12 (Box 8)
  - The Niagara Direct-Acting Pump. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - The Pioneer Tobacco Factory, Brooklyn, N.Y. Harper's Weekly, 1870-01-01 (Box 8)
  - Proclamation by the Governor for the Suppression of Certain Nuisances [petroleum refinement; Newtown Creek]. Harper's Weekly, 1881-08-13 (Box 8)
  - Richard Shannon's Greenhouses; James Dean's Greenhouses. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - The Rope and Cordage Manufactory of Wm. Wall's Sons. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - A Scene at the Atlantic Docks Brooklyn. Appleton's Journal, 1871-04-01 (Box 8)
  - Shipping Grain at Brooklyn Elevators. Harper's Weekly, 1897-10-09 (Box 8)
  - Sohmer & Co Piano Fabrik in Astoria, Long Island, gegenuber der 92 Strasse in New York [Sohmer & Co. piano factory in Astoria, Long Island, across from 92nd Street in New York]. (Box 8)
  - Terminal Facilities of New York. Harper's Weekly supplement, 1889-08-31 (Box 8)
  - The "Sweating System" in New York City. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 8)
  - Through the Years. E.R. Squibb & Sons, New York. Good Housekeeping, 1929-09 (Box 8)
  - The Union Porcelain Works and Wares. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - Unsavory Hunter's Point – The Factories and Refineries on Newtown Creek – from sketches by our special artist. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 8)
  - View of Atlantic White Lead and Linseed Oil Company's Works; Factories, Brooklyn, New York. Office, 287 Pearl Street, New York, 1874 (Box 8)
  - View of E.W. Bliss's Machine Shops and Foundries. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - View of the H.W. Peace Co.'s "Vulcan" Saw Works, Tenth and Ainslie Streets, E.D. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - View of Thos. F. Rowland's Continental Iron Works and Shipyard, Greenpoint, New York, 1874 (Box 8)
  - Warehouses and Basin of the Atlantic Dock, Brooklyn, N.Y. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851 (Box 8)
  - The William Cabble Excelsior Wire Works. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 8)
  - Worthington Hydraulic Works, South Brooklyn NY. Scientific American, 1880-09-04 (Box 8)
  - WM Wall's Sons Manufactures of Rope, Office, 220 Front Street New York Factory, Brooklyn, Undated. (Box 8)
- Libraries
  - Carnegie Libraries: DeKalb Branch; Greenpoint Branch; Williamsburg Branch; Bedford Branch; Pacific Branch. [verso – American Sugar Refining Company]. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 3)
  - The Garfield Building, Cor. Court and Remsen Streets, Brooklyn. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Gate Lodge and Hamersley Library, Sea Side Home, Bath Beach, N.Y.; Parfitt Bros. Architects. The American Architect and Building News, 1892 November 12 (Box 3)
- Memorials
  - Bronze Statue of De Witt Clinton, Designed for Greenwood Cemetery. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1853 [?] (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn's Triumphal Arch. Scientific American, 1890-01-04 (Box 4)
  - Honoring the Memory of Martyrs of the Revolution – dedication of the monument at Fort Green Park, Brooklyn NY to the imprisoned patriots who died on the British prison ship during the war for American Independence. Leslie's Weekly, 1908-11-26 (Box 4)
  - Interior View of the Tomb, in Brooklyn, L.I. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1870-08-06 (Box 4)
  - The Lincoln Monument in Prospect Park, Brooklyn, New York. Harper's Weekly, 1869-11-13 (Box 4)
  - The Metropolis in Mourning [Scenes of buildings covered in memorial décor following death of General Grant]. Harper's Weekly, 1885-08-08 (Box 4)
  - "The Navy." Symbolic Group in High Relief, Designed by Frederick MacMonnies for the Memorial Arch at the Northern Entrance to Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1899-07-15 (Box 4)
  - Proposed Monument to Sons of Brooklyn Who Fell in Four Wars, To Be Erected at Entrance to Prospect Park. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1886-02-20 (Box 4)
  - The Proposed Triumphal Arch: Soldiers and Sailors' Monument, Brooklyn, the corner stone of which was laid October 30th, Undated. (Box 4)
  - The Soldiers and Sailors Memorial Arch in Brooklyn. Preparing to lay the Corner Stone. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889-11-02 (Box 4)
  - The Soldiers' Memorial Arch, To Be Erected in Brooklyn. – From the Original Design. Harper's Weekly, 1889-08-17 (Box 4)
  - Tomb of the Martyrs, Brooklyn, Long Island., Undated. (Box 4)
- Military
  - The Armored Cruiser Brooklyn, Launched at Philadelphia. Scientific American, 1895 October 12 (Box 4)
  - The Captured Anglo-Rebel Steamer Columbia Unloading her Cargo. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1862-11-08 (Box 4)
  - The Coast Defense Question – Bird's-Eye View of New York and Surrounding Cities, Showing Their Defenseless Condition in the Event of War with a Foreign Power. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1886-12-18 (Box 4)
  - A Military Outrage – Soldiers, under Punishment, Bathing with Ball and Chain at Fort Hamilton, L.I. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1868-08-22 (Box 4)
  - The New York Columbian Celebration. Harper's Weekly, 1892 (Box 4)
  - Novel Summer Camp of Squadron C, of Brooklyn. Leslie's Weekly, 1905-09-21 (Box 4)
  - Review of the Thirteenth Regiment, N.G., at the Armory, in Brooklyn, Feb. 7th, by Gen. Fitzhugh Lee and Staff, of Virginia. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883-02-17 (Box 4)
  - Scenes and Incidents in Major-General Sheridan's Reception in New York and Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1867-10-19 (Box 4)
  - The Thirteenth Regiment New York State Militia leaving their armory in Brooklyn for the war, April 23, 1861/ The Sixty-Ninth (Irish) Regiment embarking in the "James Adger" for the war, April 23, 1861. Harper's Weekly, 1861-05-11 (Box 4)
  - View of Fort Lafayette, Situated at the Narrows, New York Harbor. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1861-09-07 (Box 4)
- Museums
  - The Children's Museum of Brooklyn Institute. Scientific American, 1900 May 12 (Box 4)
- Navy Yard
  - Activity at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Leslie's Weekly, 1898 April 7 (Box 8)
  - The Affair with Hayti—Preparations on the Expeditionary Vessels at the Brooklyn Navy-Yard—Hoisting and Placing Guns on Board. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-12-22 (Box 8)
  - Ante-Election Activity at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Breaking up the Condemned Hulks. The Daily Graphic, 1884-10-04 (Box 8)
  - At the Brooklyn Navy-Yard [2 copies; 1b&w, 1 color]. Harper's Weekly, 1892-01-30 (Box 8)
  - At the Brooklyn Navy-Yard – 1. The Puritan. 2. The Nantucket. 3. Interior of the Maine. 4. The Maine. Harper's Weekly, 1832 (Box 8)
  - Battle-Ships Crowd the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Leslie's Weekly, 1904-05-26 (Box 8)
  - Bier of Captain J.H. Ward on Board the U.S.S. North Carolina at the Brooklyn Navy Yard [German language]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, undated. (Box 8)
  - Bilder aus dem Marine-Amt in Brooklyn [Pictures from the Naval Office in Brooklyn]. Uber Land und Meer, 1898 (Box 8)
  - Bird's-Eye View from Brooklyn Bridge of the Famous Cruiser "Brooklyn" Speeding down East River. Leslie's Weekly, 1903-04-02 (Box 8)
  - Blue Jackets Playing Football in the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Collier's Weekly, 1897-01-21 (Box 8)
  - Bravo! Gut gefegt! [civil service reform; Brooklyn Navy Yard] [German language]. Puck, 1891-04-29 (Box 8)
  - The Brooklyn Navy-Yard [various images of ships, sailors, and workrooms]. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 8)
  - The Brooklyn Navy Yard and Shops. Scientific American, 1889-09-21 (Box 8)
  - Building the New War Ship "Maine" at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Harper's Weekly, 1889-03-09 (Box 8)
  - A Characteristic Group at the Brooklyn Navy Yard; "New York;" "Cincinnati;" "Brooklyn;" "Newport;" "Iowa." Scientific American, 1898-05-14 (Box 8)
  - Construction of the New War Ship Maine, at the Brooklyn Navy Yard, New York. Scientific American, 1889-10-05 (Box 8)
  - The Cruiser "Columbia" in Dry-Dock at the Brooklyn Navy-Yard for the Repair of the Damage Done to her Flat Keel Plates While Docked at Southampton, England. Leslie's Weekly, 1895-08-29 (Box 8)
  - Destruction of the Marine Barracks, Brooklyn Navy-Yard, by the Cyclone of January 9th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, January 19, 1889. (Box 8)
  - Dry Dock at Brooklyn, New York. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851-05-10 (Box 8)
  - Dry Dock No. 3; The Floating Caisson in Place Closing the Dock; The United States Cruiser Columbia in Dry Dock No. 2 Brooklyn Navy Yard. Scientific American, February 20, 1897. (Box 8)
  - A flock of Uncle Sam's peace doves at the Brooklyn Navy-Yard. [Armored cruiser Maryland; battle-ship Indiana; armored cruiser Pennsylvania; armored cruiser Colorado; battle-ship Alabama], Undated. (Box 8)
  - From Wood to Concrete—Repairs to Dry Dock No. 2, Brooklyn Navy Yard. Scientific American, 1900-10-20 (Box 8)
  - Interior Esplanade Fronting the Navy Yard, with the Ship North Carolina Alongside. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851-11-01 (Box 8)
  - Launch of the United States Cruiser Maine from the Brooklyn Navy Yard, November 17. Once A Week, 1890-12-02 (Box 8)
  - Lay Keel for World's Mightiest Plane Carrier: General View of Ceremonies at Brooklyn, N.Y. Navy Yard as the keel of the U.S.S. Saratoga, world's most powerful aircraft carrier, is laid. Illustrated Current News, 1890-03-29 (Box 8)
  - Machine Shop and Engine Room, U. S. Navy Yard, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1857-08-01 (Box 8)
  - The McCalla Naval Inquiry at Brooklyn Navy Yard. The Illustrated American, March 29, 1890. (Box 8)
  - The Million-Dollar Conflagration in the Brooklyn Navy Yard New York. Leslie's Weekly, 1899 (Box 8)
  - The Navy Helps a Mail Steamer Collier's Weekly Journal of Current Events, 1900-12-01 (Box 8)
  - Navy Yard, Brooklyn, Undated. (Box 8)
  - Navy Yard, Brooklyn, 1831. For D.T. Valentine's Manual, 1854 (Box 8)
  - Navy Yard, Brooklyn, 1834. For D.T. Valentine's Manual, 1854 (Box 8)
  - The Navy-Yard at Brooklyn, New York, June 1861. Harper's Weekly, 1861-07-20 (Box 8)
  - Navy Yard, Brooklyn, N.Y.; View Taken from the East Side of Wallabout Bay, Williamsburg; Line-of-Battle Ship North Carolina, Lying at Her Moorings as a School Ship, Brooklyn, N.Y. [2 copies]. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851-10-18 (Box 8)
  - The New Caloric Ship "Ericsson," on the Government Dry Dock, Brooklyn, N.Y. Illustrated News, 1853-01-15 (Box 8)
  - New Dry Dock at the United States Navy-Yard. Illustrated London News, 1849-10-27 (Box 8)
  - The New Dry Dock, Brooklyn Navy Yard. Scientific American, 1889-11-30 (Box 8)
  - The New Navy – Launch of the Armored Cruiser "Maine." Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1890-11-29 (Box 8)
  - The New Simpson Timber Dry Dock at the Brooklyn N.Y., Navy Yard. Scientific American, 1889-11-30 (Box 8)
  - The New Steel Floating Derrick. Scientific American, 1891-03-21 (Box 8)
  - The New Traveling Cranes at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Scientific American, 1893-06-10 (Box 8)
  - New York – Inspection of the Brooklyn Navy Yard by the New York Chamber of Commerce, Nov. 13th – The Fire Drill of the Employes and Marines. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1878-11-30 (Box 8)
  - The New York Navy Yard, Brooklyn. Scientific American, 1901-03-03 (Box 8)
  - The Niagara as She Appeared before She was Launched. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1856-03-08 (Box 8)
  - Our Largest and Most Important Navy Yard. Leslie's Weekly, undated. (Box 8)
  - The Question of a National Defense—Condition of the United States Navy; "Whitney's Rotten Row," at the Navy Yard, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1887-01-22 (Box 8)
  - Reception of the Grand Duke Alexis—Grand Ball Give by the Officers of the United States Navy to the Grand Duke, at the Navy Yard. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1871-12-16 (Box 8)
  - Reception of the Tunisian Embassy at the Brooklyn Navy Yard, Oct. 9th, by Admiral Bell, Commanding the Yard. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1865-10-28 (Box 8)
  - "Rotten Row," Brooklyn Navy Yard. Harper's Weekly, 1882-08-05 (Box 8)
  - Sailing of the Steamship "Bear," of the Greely Relief Expedition. From the Brooklyn Navy Yard, April 24th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1884-05-03 (Box 8)
  - Scenes in the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Harper's Weekly, 1861-08-24 (Box 8)
  - Second Visit to the Brooklyn Navy Yard. [interior and exterior views]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 1, 1857. (Box 8)
  - Some Pictures of the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Collier's Weekly, 1897-09-30 (Box 8)
  - Stirring Times at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. [Photographs of receiving ship "Vermont;" Dry-Docks; Cruiser "Chicago;" Dispatch-Boat "Dolphin;" and gate of Navy Yard]. Leslie's Weekly, 1898-03-17 (Box 8)
  - Thursday Evening Reception at the Sailors' Clubhouse in the Navy Yard [2 copies]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1876-08-19 (Box 8)
  - Timber Dry Doc No. 3 at United States Navy Yard, New York - View of Operations in Progress. Scientific American, 1896-02-01 (Box 8)
  - Torpedo-Boats in Winter Quarters. Leslie's Weekly, undated. (Box 8)
  - Training Electricians for the American Navy. School at the Brooklyn Navy Yard, in which Sailor Lads Learn the Mysteries of Electric Apparatus and Become Skilled Wireless-Telegraph Operators. Leslie's Weekly, 1905-05-18 (Box 8)
  - Trophies at the Brooklyn Navy Yard, New York, the Monument Erected in Memory of the Sailors and Marines who Fell, in 1859, at Barrier's Fort, China. [2 copies]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1865-07-29 (Box 8)
  - U.S. Naval Lyceum, Brooklyn N.Y. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1852 (Box 8)
  - U.S. Navy Yard Hospital, Brooklyn, situated on what was originally the shore of the Wallabout Bay. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1857 (Box 8)
  - The United States Navy Yard, Borough of Brooklyn, New York City, 1914 (Box 8)
  - The United States Navy Yard, Brooklyn – The Brooklyn Navy Yard is the chief naval station of the American republic, 1893 (Box 8)
  - The U.S. Ram, Puritan, in the New York Dry Dock, Brooklyn. Once A Week, 1890-06-10 (Box 8)
  - The U.S. Ship "Constellation," Now Loading at the Brooklyn Navy Yard with Supplies for Ireland [2 copies]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1880-04-03 (Box 8)
  - Vessels in Progress of Construction and repair at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889-07-06 (Box 8)
  - View in the Navy Yard, Brooklyn NY. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851-09-27 (Box 8)
  - View of the Navy Yard, Brooklyn NY. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1857 (Box 8)
  - A Visit to the Brooklyn Navy Yard [Entrance to the Navy Yard from York Street; "The Peacemaker;" Residence of the Commandant]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1857-02-14 (Box 8)
  - A Visit to the Brooklyn Navy Yard; General view of the Brooklyn Navy Yard, from the rear of the Marine Hospital. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1857-02-14 (Box 8)
  - Ye Story of Ye Navy Yard Which is at Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1859-03-12 (Box 8)
- New York City: Consolidation
  - Selfish Objections to a Good Match. Puck, circa 1898 [?] (Box 4)
- Parks: Fort Greene
  - Photograph of park. Color painted photograph by Detroit Photographic Company [2 copies], 1904 [?] (Box 4)
- Parks: Prospect Park
  - An Afternoon Concert at the Lake, Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1897 (Box 4)
  - Anniversary Day in Brooklyn, May 27th—Parade of Sixty Thousand Sunday-School Children. The Scene in Prospect Park. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1885-06-06 (Box 4)
  - Annual Parade of the First Brigade, N.G., S.N.Y., at Prospect Park, Mat 12th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1881-05-28 (Box 4)
  - Bits of the Brooklyn Sunday School Parade on "Anniversary Day," May 24. The Commercial Advertiser, 1901-06-01 (Box 4)
  - Circular Yacht in Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1878-07-27 (Box 4)
  - The Grand Sham Battle of the Second Division, N.G., at Prospect Park, Brooklyn, February 23rd—Scene on the Long Meadow—the Mob Breaking in on the First Line of Defense. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1885-03-07 (Box 4)
  - Jahresfest der Sonnfagsldulen in Brooklyn, NY; Szene in Prospect Park [Annual Celebration of the Sunday Schools in Brooklyn, NY; Scene in Prospect Park]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, undated. (Box 4)
  - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, Undated. (Box 4)
  - Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Accompanying Appleton's Journal. June 4, 1870. "A Little News:" From the Friends of Central, Prospect, Cadwalader, Fort Greene, Druid Hill, and Branch Brook Parks. Publication: 2000; image a reproduction of an 1870 illustration. (Box 4)
  - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, New York [Various views of the park]. Harper's Weekly, 1868-09-12 (Box 4)
  - Sham Battle at Prospect Park, Brooklyn, on Washington's Birthday. Harper's Weekly, 1885-03-07 (Box 4)
  - Sketches in Prospect Park, Brooklyn. The Daily Graphic, 1874-06-02 (Box 4)
  - Third Annual Meeting of the National Archery Association, at Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1881-07-30 (Box 4)
  - A View in Prospect Park, Brooklyn, N.Y. (Cleft Ridge Span). Cricket on the Hearth, 1874-07 (Box 4)
- Police
  - Tub Race at Gowanus Bay, by the Members of the South Brooklyn Police Force, September 20th, 1869. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1869 October 9 (Box 8)
  - View of Camp John F. Hylan, Sheepshead Bay Park, Where 1,000 Policemen a Day Live in the Tented City and Undergo Strict Military Discipline. The New York Times, 1918 September 22 (Box 8)
- Political Corruption
  - A Cinch says Boss Croker to Boss Mclaughlin: "Shake." Harper's Weekly, 1893 September 30 (Box 4)
  - A Desperate Situation. W. Reid; Schieren. Puck, 1893-12-27 (Box 4)
  - The Man with the Muck-Rake. Judge, 1894 (Box 4)
  - New York City - Echoes of the Late Presidential Elections - Paying A Grotesque Wager on the Result - Scene on the Brookly Bridge, November 14th Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-11-24 (Box 4)
  - A Nice Attitude for a United States Senator. Puck, 1893-08-30 (Box 4)
  - Oh, I am a Rural Assemblyman From Wayback Country Fair with no conscience at all, and one ounce of brains and the hayseed in my hair. Puck, 1887-05-11 (Box 4)
  - Out of the Darkness: Will the Cloud of Bossism Again Enfold Brooklyn? Puck, 1883 (Box 4)
  - Wed! "Does oo love oo Tify-wigy" Puck, November 1, 1893 (Box 4)
- Portraits
  General
  All from Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884, unless otherwise noted.
  - Ambrose, Daniel (M.D.), 1884 (Box 4)
  - Ammerman, Albert. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, John C. (Box 4)
  - Baird, Andrew D. and Robinson Gill. (Box 4)
  - Barnes, A.S. (Box 4)
  - Barnes, Alfred C. (Gen.) (Box 4)
  - Barnes, Demas (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Barney, Nathan. (Box 4)
  - Bartlett, Homer L. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Bauery, Paul. (Box 4)
  - Beard, Sylvester M. (Box 4)
  - Beard, William. (Box 4)
  - Bedell, Chester. (Box 4)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (Rev.) (Box 4)
  - Beekman, Abraham J. (Box 4)
  - Bergen, Teunis G. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Bergen, Tunis G. (Box 4)
  - Binns, James. (Box 4)
  - Birdsall, S.T. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Birdseye, Lucien. (Box 4)
  - Blackford, Eugene G. (Box 4)
  - Boerum, Henry. (Box 4)
  - Bossert, Louis. (Box 4)
  - Bowlsby, William H. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Boynton, Eben Moody (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Brant, George W. (Box 4)
  - Brick, J.K. (Box 4)
  - Britton, Winchester. (Box 4)
  - Broach, John. (Box 4)
  - Brown, George W. (Box 4)
  - Bulkley, Edwin. (Box 4)
  - Bunker, Edward Seaman. (Box 4)
  - Burroughs, Horace F. (Box 4)
  - Burrows, Chester D. Jr. (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Edwin H. (Box 4)
  - Byrne, John (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Cabble, Elijah. (Box 4)
  - Cabble, William. (Box 4)
  - Campbell, J.W. (Box 4)
  - Campbell, Felix (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Chapman, Isaac F. (Box 4)
  - Claghorn, Charles. (Box 4)
  - Coger, George W. (Box 4)
  - Conselyea, William. (Box 4)
  - Cooper, Nicholas. (Box 4)
  - Creamer, William G. (Box 4)
  - Cristian, H.S. (Box 4)
  - Daggett, Albert (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Dakin, Thomas S. (Maj. Gen.) (Box 4)
  - Delmar, John. (Box 4)
  - Dennis, Charles S. (Box 4)
  - Dick, William. (Box 4)
  - Doherty, John. (Box 4)
  - DuBois, Ithamar. (Box 4)
  - Dudly, William Henry (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Duryea, Harmanus (General) (Box 4)
  - Duryea, Samuel Bowne. (Box 4)
  - Eadie, James C. (Box 4)
  - Eddy, George M. (Box 4)
  - Elwell, James. (Box 4)
  - Engeman, William A. (Box 4)
  - Farmer, Aaron D. (Box 4)
  - Feltman, Charles. (Box 4)
  - The Fingleton Brothers (Patrick J.; Henry W.; Hugh S.) (Box 4)
  - Fisher, Francis B. (Box 4)
  - Fisk, William M.L. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Forrester, George B. (Box 4)
  - Fowler, George Ryerson (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Fraim, George W. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Freel, Edwood. (Box 4)
  - Frost, John S. (Box 4)
  - Gallagher, Bernard. (Box 4)
  - General John B. Woodward, Independent Candidate for Mayor of Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1885-10-31 (Box 4)
  - Gil, Robinson and Andrew D. Baird. (Box 4)
  - Gilbert, Jasper Willet (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Gilmore, Quincy Adams (Gen.) (Box 4)
  - Good, John. (Box 4)
  - Gorton, David A. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Hardy, John J. (Box 4)
  - Harrison, Gabriel. (Box 4)
  - Harkness, William. (Box 4)
  - Haskins, Samuel M. (Box 4)
  - Hazzard, William H. (Box 4)
  - Herr, Frederick. (Box 4)
  - Hester, William (Col.) (Box 4)
  - Hobbs, Edward H. (Box 4)
  - Hogan, Timothy. (Box 4)
  - Holton, Francis H. (Box 4)
  - Howell, James. (Box 4)
  - Hulbert, Henry C. (Box 4)
  - Humphreys, Asahel Willard. (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson, Joseph C. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - James, Darwin R. (Box 4)
  - Jennings, Abraham G. (Box 4)
  - Jennings, Ephraim J. (Box 4)
  - Keegan, William (Very Rev.) (Box 4)
  - Ketcham, Enoch. (Box 4)
  - Ketcham, Isaac A. (Box 4)
  - Kiernan, John. (Box 4)
  - Kingsley, W.E. (Box 4)
  - Kinsella, Thomas. (Box 4)
  - Kissam, Brewster. (Box 4)
  - Laimbeer, Richard Harper. (Box 4)
  - Leary, James D. (Box 4)
  - Lee, John. (Box 4)
  - Littlejohn, Adam N. (Rt. Rev. D.D) (Box 4)
  - Livingstone, Walter L. (Esq.) (Box 4)
  - Loeser, Frederick. (Box 4)
  - Loomis, John S. (Box 4)
  - Low, Abiel Abbott. (Box 4)
  - Low, Seth [2 portraits]. (Box 4)
  - Lynch, Benjmain T. (Box 4)
  - Lyon, William H. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - McCabe, Daniel. (Box 4)
  - McChesny, James. (Box 4)
  - McKane, John Y. (Box 4)
  - McLeer, James (Col.) (Box 4)